<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pablo Pérez</title><link>https://pa-perz.com/</link><description>Recent content on Pablo Pérez</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pa-perz.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Services</title><link>https://pa-perz.com/services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 16:47:13 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://pa-perz.com/services/</guid><description>Soon, I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to freelance some projects. In the meanwhile, you can check some projects I&amp;rsquo;ve made on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Setup</title><link>https://pa-perz.com/setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 15:28:29 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://pa-perz.com/setup/</guid><description>// TODO</description></item><item><title>Work</title><link>https://pa-perz.com/work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 15:27:43 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://pa-perz.com/work/</guid><description>Work AYESA S.L. (Nov. 2021-Present) Microservices Backend Developer (Spring Boot, Java) (Remote)
On a microservices-oriented application used for tasks related to electric vehicles, I:
Created and developed APIs, while improving test coverage of existing APIs. Reduced reported bugs and vulnerabilities in many microservices by 92.85% at a critical point during the application development. Created developer tools to ease the creation of mappers between microservice messages. Created services and connections between microservices using Apache Kafka and Google gRPC, verifying their correct functioning and use.</description></item><item><title>🐢Why I decided to create a blog in the age of social media</title><link>https://pa-perz.com/posts/2022-07-11/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pa-perz.com/posts/2022-07-11/</guid><description>Today, it is difficult to find a moment of rest for the person that tries to be productive. We get bombarded with information daily. Ads, new products, social feeds, emails&amp;hellip; As soon as we have consumed the information we just had in front of our face, the media world has more data in line ready to be consumed.
This produces the problem we all have felt at some time during our stay on the internet: brain fog.</description></item></channel></rss>